6/7/23, 6:27 PM RESUME



BONY SAMEER BODRA

Full Stack Developer

Pangalore, INDIA ■ connectbsameer@gmail.com +91-8296491353

PROFILE SKILLS

As a part of DIGIKULL(software training institute), I succeed to grow my programming skills in different areas.

I have successfully completed the 1 year programming course (full stack) by attending all the live session and live coding in which I have completed all the assignments as well as projects on time in which i have complete 40+ assignments and major projects both FRONT END and BACK END part.

My practical experience is Learning new programming language and I am motivated to mastering those skills and to enrich my knowledge with a new one.

I have also mentored 8 students in Digikull (Software training institute).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Customer Support - Social Media, Myntra

2020 - 2021, Bengaluru Urban

Relationship Manager, Indian Money

2021 - 2022, Bengaluru Urban

- Maintained client correspondence, preference and sales on CRM system for sales and marketing purpose.
- Scheduled, Arranged and attended meeting with customers to maintain training and long-lasting relationships.

EDUCATION

St. Francis School, 10th - ICSE

2010, Ranchi

Oxford Public School, 10+2 - CBSE

2012, Ranchi

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Ant Design

Material UI

Javascripr

JQuery

React.js

Node.is

Express.js

MongoDB

JSON

Data Structure and

Algorithm

Git

HOBBIES

Visiting new places

Reading

Cooking

Driving

LANGUAGES

6/7/23, 6:27 PM RESUME

Dayananda Sagar College of Engineering, B.E - EEE

2012 - 2015, Bengaluru

English

Hindi

COURSES

Full Stack Web Development, Digikull - Software Training Institute

2022 - 2023

GITHUB: https://github.com/bonysameer

FRONTEND MENTOR: https://www.frontendmentor.io/profile/bonysameer

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bony-sameer-2b5209b0/

PERSONAL WEBSITE: https://bonysameer.github.io/website-bony-sameer/

PERSONAL PROJECTS

WEATHER APP

- HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT
- Developed a responsive and user friendly Website.
- Developed a Weather app that tracks the user's location.
- It shows the details of Current Temperature, Speed of the Wind, Clouds and Humidity details

TINDOG

- HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | BOOTSTRAP
- Build a responsive and user friendly website
- Its a website just like a tinder where user can match the dogs for Breeding purpose.

DRUM-KIT

- HTML | CSS | BOOTSTRAP | JAVASCRIPT
- Developed a responsive and user friendly website.
- Added a different sound of Drum Kit where user can play the music just like music keyboard with keypad and also with the mouse.

TODO APP

- ReactJs | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS
- Designed a responsive ToDo app which is user friendly app.
- This ToDo app lets user to create, read, save their daily tasks
- User can also update and tick mark the task which is completed.
- User can also Delete their task once the task is completed

SORTING VISUALIZER

- JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS | BOOTSTRAP
- This Sorting-visualizer project is basically a web development which is used to visualize the sorting algorithms and performs the operation of algorithms step by step.
- User can visualize the Bubble sort, Selection sort, Insertion Sort, Quick sort, Merge sort with diagram.

6/7/23, 6:27 PM RESUME

INVENTORY MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

- MERN PROJECT ReactJS | HTML | CSS | MongoDB | MONGOOSE
- Build a project with proper authentications where user can create their account and login to their account.
- User deatail will save in the database
- User can create and Update their password

Declaration

I do hearby declare that all the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge. I would like to seize this world of oppurtunity and make it my way of life

PLACE: Bangalore - 560111